Elias Johnson

Computer Science Undergraduate

+(541) 974-2350 | eliascarljohnson@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/eliasjohnson- | https://elias-johnson.github.io/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a passionate and diligent individual driven by the desire to serve others, a lifelong learner, and a problem solver with a sharp eye for the meticulous. I am proficient in multiple programming languages and paradigms such as object-oriented design and procedural/functional programming. Well-versed in version control and Agile methodologies, I have experience with the product development process, delivering quality work with a diverse team.

EDUCATION

GEORGE FOX UNIVERSITY

Newberg, OR

August 2022 - Present

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Cybersecurity

Minor in Music

GPA: 3.86

TECHNICAL SKILLS

ProgrammingPython, Java, JavaScript, C++, Scala, ShellDevelopmentAgile Methodologies, Git, UML, Unit Testing

Web-Development HTML, CSS
Database SQL, PostgreSQL

Networking Subnetting, Routing Algorithms, Topology Design

Cybersecurity Autopsy, Burp Suite, Wireshark
Operating Systems Windows, Linux (Ubuntu, Debian)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BON APPÉTIT

Associate, Part-Time

Newberg, OR

August 2022 - Present

At Bon Appétit, I work a variety of roles including ensuring the cleanliness of the dish room and kitchen, preparing food and drink at the café, and running the till and stocking shelves for the student store.

Skills: Organization, Time Management, Customer Service

ALBANY PARTY STORE

Albany, OR

Associate, Seasonal

June 2018 - August 2024

At The Albany Party Store, I worked as one of the primary delivery drivers for rental items. I would also spend much of my time in the showroom, assisting customers on the phone or in-person with their orders.

Skills: Communication, Critical Thinking, Customer Service